A deadly race to the truth.
Fatal Frenemies is a thriller, tv movie, drama film directed by Richard Switzer.
After Haley goes missing, Michelle must work quickly to find her daughter and discover the
truth behind the mysterious deaths before Haley or anyone else gets hurt.
Michelle Langford, played by Laurie Fortier.
Haley Langford, played by Jane Dillon.
Luke, played by Huntington Daly.
Brooke, played by Ashton Leigh.
Elaina, played by Sahara Ale.
Abby, played by Rachel Ogechi Kanu.
Alexis Louder (born August 31, 1991) is an American
actress from Charlotte, North Carolina.
She is known for 2021's The Tomorrow War and Copshop.
The film explores themes of high school, jealousy,
murder, rage, high school friends.
The tone is emotional and intense.